I've been waiting for you [ __ ] Badman
we don't have to fight we can love Sonic
Underground as equals as friends there
is enough to go around
oh my God hey I'll help me oh my God
somebody please save my ass you're going
to pay for that now you will see what
happens when you mess with somebody who
loves Sonic Underground you think your
love is stronger than mine
get your sweaty balls out of my face he
only balls I like our Sonic
Underground's so leave but where I rape
you in the ass hold on a minute what's
that oh my God you think this will stop
it
I go through more hardships trying not
to cry during the ending of science
Sonic Underground
he's so powerful but how every night I
watch Sonic Underground TVs while eating
chili dogs then I see my favorites Sonic
Underground songs while I'm in the
bathroom taking a [ __ ] every night
before I go to Sleet I pray not to God
but to Sonic Underground
I see now you're Sonic Underground [ __ ]
well here is some news for you
so Am I you make that sound like a bad
thing I'll [ __ ] kill you [ __ ]
take this
go out [ __ ] boy make fun of Sonic
Underground in front of me again I beg
of you let me [ __ ] you in the ass like
the [ __ ] you are it's what you deserve
[Music]
hey where did you go it looks like you
have the wrong idea about me Superman
[Music]
what is this what the hell did you just
do you don't get it do you
I'm a big Sonic Underground fan
everything I learned in terms of
fighting I learned by watching the Sonic
Underground or to be more specific
Manic the Hedgehog he's the [ __ ]
badass
I'll kill you no you won't because what
I shot you with was a packet of spicy
chilli seasoning mix
extra spicy I was going to eat chili
dogs tonight for dinner just like my
hero Sonic but now I can't because of
you now you will pay with your life
take this I learned this move by
watching mana kick this war bottle
episode 31 funny you think I'm done with
you
think again get up [ __ ] what did I just
say [ __ ] please just leave me alone
Sonic Underground fans never resort to
begging thanks for showing you that you
aren't even a real Sonic Underground fan
now I don't have to worry about killing
you Sonic wouldn't give up finding his
mother so I won't give up on beating
your ass that's the spirit
Sonic Underground fans a never surrender
you are right perhaps we aren't so
different after all but even still there
can only be one one and only true fan
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] suck my
balls [ __ ] Oh Oh No please please don't
hurt me
won't happen what happened to Sonic
Underground fans never beg huh
that is it I'm tired of this turn around
so I can't bang you in the ass no don't
touch me
shut up after I kill you and going
straight to your house to take all of
your Sonic Underground [ __ ] that
includes every one of your DVDs and all
of your plush toys do you hear me
I won't let you kill me if you must but
leave Sonic Underground out of this
[Music]